Shit.
I'm not sure you should be...
I'm fine. Much better.
Okay, but...
Do you have somewhere you can
go?
AAT.
Hi, I'm here for the meeting.
Come on, come on. Hand them
over.
Dave, so glad you could make
it. Good to see you.
Well it's not like I have much
of a fucking choice is it?
Come on Henry, you know the
rules.
Okay, speak to you later.
Henry, do we have to do this
every week?
I dunno, do we?
Kara.
This is a surprise.
Hey Ellen.
Been a while.
After last time I honestly
didn't think we'd see you again.
Didn't think I'd be welcome.
Depends.
You planning on causing trouble?
It's been a rough night.
More than that, I'd say.
I just wanted somewhere to come
get my head straight.
If you don't want me here then,
whatever.
Jesus.
Grab yourself a coffee, find
somewhere to sit, we start in twenty.
And hey...
Don't make me regret this.
Thanks.
Takes nothing to fall off the wagon,
and a lot to walk back through that door.
Figure anyone with that much
courage is worth my time.
Right.
This shit.
Every week this fucking shit.
You done?
Eddy, I said "Are you done?"
Eddy, I'm fucking talking to
you...
- I... I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
- It's alright.
It's just a spilt drink.
It happens.
Right?
Fucking junkies.
Waste of my time.
Heard a commotion. Figured it
might be you.
Seth.
Sobriety suits you.
Who the fuck is that guy?
Dave?
Yeah, don't mind him.
Used to be police.
Maybe still is.
He's probably busted everyone
in the room at some point.
Yeah, I remember him.
Really?
Mm-hm.
What did he get you on?
Shoplifting.
And assaulting a police officer.
- Jesus.
- I know.
Well now here he is sitting
opposite you in a frigging circle.
Addiction. The great equaliser,
right?
What about you Eddy? Thought
you cleaned up.
I have, I've just not been
feeling too well.
- Think I'm coming down with something.
- Yeah, whatever man...
Listen, if Ellen catches you, you're
gonna be out on your arse, okay?
Go.
Get straightened out. I'll
cover for you, alright?
We've all been there.
Trying your hardest but the only time people
seem to notice is when you're fucking up.
He'll get there.
Yeah.
Helps with the aches.
Thanks.
So, how long you been on the
script?
Couple of weeks.
How much they got you on?
Not enough.
Sounds about right.
Look, it's tough but try and
get by without it.
So, what's going on Kay?
It's six months, no-one hears
from you and then you just rock up?
You been using?
Just a wash. Nothing serious.
Just hospital serious, right?
Fuck.
Yeah, you don't use when you're
on the script.
- You of all people should know that.
- Yeah, okay...
Okay, I fucked up.
I thought I could handle it and
I couldn't.
Lesson learnt.
Yeah?
What's the difference this time?
This time?
I want it.
I need it.
Come on.
Better get back inside, yeah?
Hey, Seth?
Do you ever think about
stuff?
Hasn't done you any good.
See you're back already hanging
off Seth.
It's not like that.
Yeah, whatever.
He's been working really hard.
He's doing his steps.
The last thing he needs is a
distraction.
I guess you're the expert.
How long have you been clean
now?
Red for ninety days.
Blur for six months, right?
What's black for?
Two years.
Any advice?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I doubt you'll even be here
next week.
Okay, let's get started.
Is everybody...?
Here?
Goddammit Eddy.
You know, some of us actually
have places to be tonight.
Alright everyone. Up on your
feet. Let's do this.
Come on.
Grant me serenity
to accept the things I cannot change.
The courage to change the
things I can.
And the wisdom to know the
difference.
We've all done things we are
not proud of.
Those who have them, get out
your lists.
Go on.
Hold them up in the air.
This is it.
All the people we've hurt.
People we knew.
People who cared for us.
People we'll never see again.
Knowing that is not enough.
You need to be ready to take
the next step. To make amends.
Tough, right?
Probably the toughest thing
you've done.
But not the toughest thing
you're going to do.
We're going to have to make
good on it.
Yes.
But don't worry, we're not
there yet.
This is the past.
And recovery isn't just about the past. It can
be about the here and now... About the future.
Alright, tag meeting.
We're gonna go around the group.
I don't wanna hear the bad, I
wanna hear the good.
I wann hear one thing.
One good thing you've all done
recently.
Hey, come on!
It's two hundred steps across
that parking lot.
Two hundred.
These twelve should be a piece
of cake.
Come on. Who's up?
I've been helping out my sister
quite a bit.
She's got a kid and the Dad's
long gone, y'know?
So I've been taking him on
evenings.
Playing football with him and
that.
It's not much.
It doesn't pay the bills or
anything but, erm.
It's something, I guess.
So, yeah.
Tag.
Okay, erm, last week I had my
first unsupervised visit with my son.
He's been living with his
Grandma.
I hadn't seen him for two months.
Her for about three years.
So I was nervous about going.
As soon as I got to the path,
she was there.
The door's open. Arms wide.
And for a split second I thought it
was because she wanted to see me.
And then I realised it was that
she didn't want anyone else to.
I guess there are some things
you can't make right, so why try?
Anyway, positive.
My son.
It's going well.
It's good.
Henry, tag?
Yeah, I'm not doing this.
Listen, I'll sit in this circle and I'll
fucking nod and get my stamp...
What's your problem?
No cross-talk please.
Same as everyone else.
I got caught.
You think you're different?
Tag fucking tag.
- What have you done this week?
- Yeah.
That's it. Keep pushing
sunshine.
Is that a threat? Did you just
fucking threaten me?
Alright, okay. Let's cut this
off now.
Kara, why don't you go next?
Y'know what? I'm...
I'm not really feeling this
whole...
We're not here to sit in
judgement.
You've nothing to be afraid of.
Maybe I deserve to be judged.
You ever thought about that?
Maybe there's no coming back
from what I did?
Yeah, this was a terrible idea.
I shouldn't have come.
Please. Don't. Stay.
Alright, knock it off Charley.
Come on...
Kara...
- Please...
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
Somethings you can't make
right, so why try?
Interrupting something?
We're fine.
Can I help you?
This AAT, right?
Yes.
Name's Jack.
Well...
Hello Jack.
I'm late.
Wasn't sure I was gonna be
coming to be honest, but...
So how's this work then? We all sit
in a circle and have a bit of a moan?
It's called taking inventory
mate.
It's a lot of hard work.
Appreciate if you took it
seriously.
Yeah, I heard that commotion
from up the hallway.
He pisses you off...
You wanna kill him...
She wants to leave...
Sounds like moaning if you ask
me.
Don't think we did.
It is moaning...
Bitching...
Whatever you wanna call it.
From the outside, maybe that's
all it looks like.
Maybe that's hard to hear but.
Accepting ourselves means
accepting we aren't perfect.
Speak for yourself.
When you accept that, you
accept you can improve, move on.
And what if you're a monster?
You just supposed to accept
that?
That's not self acceptance,
that's self judgement.
We don't do that here.
I wasn't talking about me.
Cool. Right, so I'm gonna to
go...
Not that this hasn't been weird
and extremely awkward but...
Yeah...
You're not going anywhere.
Jack...
- Jack, you don't wanna do this...
- Shut up.
Turn around.
Look at me.
I haven't seen your face.
You could just walk out of here
and I wouldn't say anything.
Look. At. Me.
So you're the funny guy, eh?
Always telling jokes. Never
taking it seriously.
Not so funny anymore, is it?
Jack, you need to calm down.
Whatever it is that you want.
This isn't the way to go about
it.
No, I'd say it's exactly the
way to go about it.
Well let's talk about that.
Let's talk about what you want.
I want you to take this
seriously.
You come in here. Sit in your
circle.
Talking about fucking higher
powers.
Thinking that's enough.
You've no idea what real
recovery is.
What it takes.
How much it fuckling hurts.
And not just you...
Sit the fuck down.
You.
Take these. Tie them up.
It's okay...
It's gonna be okay...
Just gotta keep the pressure
on... just keep the pressure on...
Just gotta keep the pressure on.
Get in the circle.
The erm...
If I move, she'll bleed to
death.
Get in the circle.
There's probably a first aid kit
in the kitchen, If I could just...
Fuck.
Do you want something?
For the pain?
Well, I'm sure someone here's
got something...
Ask them.
You're dying.
No-one would judge you.
Ask them.
Is someone else here?
Yes? No?
What am I going to find if I go
out through there?
Nothing.
What was that?
We'll see about that.
Probably wondering why I'm here.
Who I am.
Believe it or not, I'm here to
help you.
You come here every week,
looking for change.
Something to make a difference.
Well, here it is.
Your "higher power".
Why are you doing this?
We haven't done anything wrong.
You sure about that?
Shit.
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna go around the circle.
Talk about what's in here.
What you've done.
And I want each of you to tell
me.
Show me.
Why you deserve to walk out
that door.
Why I should let you.
Don't look at them. They can't
help you.
Do you want to tell them who
this is for?
I think you do.
I think you want to tell us
I think you want to get it off
your chest.
Get it out in the open.
My son. It's for my son.
Your son?
He live with you?
With my mother.
With your mother?
Why is he with your mother?
Why does he live with your
mother?
I was a mess.
I needed to get high so I left
him in the house.
You left him in the house?
It wasn't going to be for long.
I thought he'd be okay.
I just lost track of time and
when I got back...
He was so brave.
He didn't cry for the first few
hours.
The neighbours heard and...
He's my son.
He belongs with his mother.
What would you say to him?
If he was here right now?
It's difficult, I know,
bringing all this back up.
Okay, okay.
We're gonna try something.
You're gonna talk to me as if I
was your boy.
What?
Well, it's an exercise.
He isn't here.
This way you can talk to him.
Get everything off your chest.
I don't know...
She doesn't have to do this.
Yes she does.
I want you to apologise.
To me
your son
right now.
I'm sorry Liam I...
Why are you sorry?
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
- You had a choice.
- No, I didn't.
Yes you did, yes you did
you had a choice to be a
mother...
You had a choice to be a mother
or smack head
- and you chose drugs over me, isn't that right?
- No...
It's not... it's not...
Why do you hate me?
I don't.
Yes you do.
- I don't. I love you. Please, don't say that.
- Ever since you found out you were knocked up.
You've hated me.
Ever since I was born.
Why do you hate me?
Please don't say that.
- Why do you hate me? Why do you hate me?
- I'd do anything for you. I don't hate you.
WHY DO YOU HATE ME?
Because you make me realise
what a fucking terrible person I am.
I didn't... I didn't mean... I
didn't mean...
I didn't...
Don't judge me.
Don't you dare judge me.
You don't have the fucking
right. None of you.
The things you've done.
No-one's judging you.
Fuck you man, she's right.
None of you has the right to
judge anyone.
Henry, what are you doing?
Leave it.
Won't do you any good listening
to him.
He's scared.
Talking shit.
Aren't you Henry?
No, I'm talking complete
fucking sense.
I'm not dying for you, you
piece of shit.
This is your mess.
That's what this is about right?
They've done something to you?
Fucked you over?
I get it.
You're pissed off.
Really, really pissed off.
But I'm not the guy you want.
Is that so?
Henry, stop talking now.
Maybe the plastic cop got a bit
too big for his boots, eh?
Arrested somebody he shouldn't
have?
Wouldn't be the first time
would it Davey?
You've got some fucking balls
son.
And this bitch. "Some things
you can't make right?"
Her own fucking words.
And this guy, oh you'll love
this one.
Henry, you need to calm the
fuck down mate.
Steals a fuck ton of drugs from
his dealer
- and let's his buddy take the rap for it.
- You need to stop this now.
How many bin bags was it they
found him in again?
You prick. You fucking prick.
It's caught up with you man.
I'm not like these junkies.
These fucking liars.
All this talking...
It's just hot air isn't it?
A whole lot of nothing.
Oh god... oh god...
You can't talk your way out of
this one
not with me Henry.
She didn't tell me she was
married
I swear to you, I swear.
I tired to break it off
I tried you know
but she said she'd...
I didn't think she'd actually
do it
otherwise I would've...
It wasn't my fault.
She wasn't my wife.
She wasn't?
No.
But she was somebody's.
You're just like the rest of
them, Henry.
You're a piece of shit.
Say it Henry, say: "I'm a piece
of shit".
I'm a piece of shit.
You're a piece of shit.
I feel like we're making
progress, don't you?
Right, who's next?
Fuck it.
And fuck you too.
When I first came here.
I couldn't help but feel that
you were all
labouring under the
misapprehension
that you somehow didn't deserve
this.
That you were decent people.
Well, I'm glad we've managed to
come to an understanding
on that front.
Well, some of you at least.
You've got a daughter.
It's not a question, it's an
observation.
See, men with daughters have
this 'look'.
They wanna protect them so they
see everyone
pretty much as a threat.
Isn't that right Dave?
Careful!
You'll hurt yourself.
Or someone else.
You know, you can frighten this
lot
throwing chairs around
pointing that pop-gun at
people...
But me?
I've got your number mate.
I really don't think you have.
I tell you what
why don't I make a start
just join in when you feel up
to it, okay?
"To Jenny"
"my daughter."
"I've respected your wishes and
kept my distance."
"It hasn't always been easy."
"You are and always have been
the dearest thing in my life."
"I wish you could say the same
about me."
"In the past I failed myself."
"I failed you."
"I was worthless."
"Not fit to be your father."
This is really good stuff, Dave.
Really riveting.
You should channel this into
poetry or something.
"I don't remember the things
you said I did to you."
"I want to believe that it
wasn't me who did them."
"That I couldn't do that to my
own daughter"
"but I know that's not true."
What did you do, David?
What did you do, Dave?
It was the drink.
Not me.
I didn't know what I was
doing...
I didn't know what I was...
She was your daughter, you sick
bastard!
Do it.
Just do it.
I thought this was
about what's fair.
Please.
Now I know it's just about you
getting your rocks off.
If you'd have read what was in
here
you'd know he deserved that.
Somethings you can't make right.
Makes you wonder...
You think you've got something?
Call a cop.
This is her first night here.
Alright?
She doesn't have a letter.
She doesn't know anything.
She came in here.
She sat in that chair.
Figure she's got something to
get off her chest.
Something she wants to tell us
all?
You stole something?
Hurt someone?
Fucked someone?
Do that to yourself?
Well whatever it is, you must
really hate yourself for it.
I came here for the free coffee.
You came here because you've
got nowhere else to go.
Do you want to take something
from me?
Friends?
Family?
Self respect?
I have nothing left for you to
take.
You think you've hit rock
bottom?
Well guess what?
I brought a fucking shovel.
- Hey, woah, woah...
- What are you doing?
What the fuck?
Jack, what are you doing?
Where are you taking me man?
Jack... Jack, you're talking to
me, not him.
Oh fuck...
Nothing left for me to take
that's what you said.
So, I guess I'll take it from
him.
Oh shit... oh shit...
No, no don't do this.
Please!
I... erm... I don't know what you
want.
I wanna know why you're here.
What you did that was so
terrible.
I stole things.
What things?
What things? Erm...
- Try Harder.
- Okay, okay.
Try harder.
Okay, okay... Just... just... just
let me think...
I swear to Christ, I will burn
his fucking face off.
What do you want?
I want to know why you're here.
What did you do?
What did you do that was so
fucking bad?
It was my fault.
What was your fault?
I...
No...
No... no... no... NO!
If anything happens whilst I'm
gone, anything I don't like.
I won't hesitate to shoot every
last one of you.
Do you understand?
Good.
Oh Christ!
What the fuck are you doing?
You heard what he said.
Eddy?
Great, the cavalry's arrived.
I managed to distract him.
I don't know for how long.
We gotta go.
We gotta go now.
You need a hand there buddy?
No. Everything's fine here,
I've got it under control.
Fuck,
fuck, FUCK! He's fucking locked it!
Jesus. They really did a number
on her.
Like I said. Everything's fine...
Bunch of fucking animals around
here.
Didn't always used to be like
this, let me tell you.
Hey.
Do you want me to call the
police?
Oh that won't be necessary...
It's good to see you man.
He can't be here.
You can't be here!
If he finds you, he'll kill us.
He'll kill us all!
He'll fucking kill us anyway.
Fuck!
I can't... They won't...
Eddy...
The phones...
The lock box... the lock box on
the table.
Uh, the keys?
I...
Where are the fucking keys?
I don't know.
Come on, come!
He's got them!
Don't do this to me!
It's in the cupboard.
There's a phone in the cupboard.
To the left of the door.
Come on, Eddy.
- That's a fucking shame...
- You really don't have to...
See, the insurance companies man
they'll screw you without a
police report.
You've done enough already.
Where is it?
Where is it?!
Do you see it?
How do we even know it's there?
It's there. Trust me.
I got it.
I got it!
Why can't you get any fucking
signal down here!
Eddy...
It's time for you to take your
phone.
To go home...
Uh... it's fine... I don't.
What? You don't want your phone?
Or you don't want to go home?
I just... I don't...
You 'just' what?
You 'don't' what?
I don't want any trouble.
Please.
Eddy...
The window!
It's the only place where you
can get any fucking signal.
Come on!
Please work... please work...
It's a joke.
Joke?
Yeah.
Joke.
Here.
Take it.
Get yourself off home.
Please work... please work...
What was that?
It was nothing.
Everything's fine.
I should probably be...
No, no, no...
What's happening?
He's... he's killed him.
Oh fuck... no...
Please...
Eddy...
Eddy!
You need to get back to the
roof.
I can't... there's no time...
Then you need to make the call.
You need to make the call now.
We're fucked. We're completely
fucked.
Well, we're not getting out of
this on our own.
If he comes back and realises
we've called for help
you think he's going to wait
for the police?
He's gonna put a bullet in each
of our fucking heads!
We need to rethink this.
Don't listen to him Eddy.
There's no time, you're gonna
get us all fucking killed.
Eddy, you need to keep it
together.
I'm not putting my life in this
fuck up's hands.
Back off Henry.
Don't listen to them Eddy,
listen to me.
You can do this.
This is suicide.
Eddy... please...
Make the bleeding call.
It's 999.
How on earth are you fucking
this up?
Do it!
Fuck, fuck fuck...
DO IT!
999!
Yes, YES!
Here?
Unbe-fucking-lievable.
Jesus.
That's a lot of gear.
So you're like what?
A drug dealer now?
So, how does that work then?
You keep close to the ones who
look like they're struggling.
Offer to help them out?
And all this time I was blaming
myself.
I never gave anyone anything
they didn't ask for.
Do you really believe that?
Or is it just something you say
to make it easier?
It's funny, when I first came
here I actually felt safe.
Like for once, somebody
actually had my back.
Guess I know the truth now
though.
What's that?
We're just a bunch of people,
sat in a circle
waiting for our turn to talk.
Disappointing.
Not exactly unexpected but still
disappointing.
I found this
in the bathroom.
In the bathroom!
Just can't help yourself, can
you?
You get this from him?
S-sometimes.
Sometimes.
Does that sound like something
a friend would do?
Someone trying to help you?
No.
You're in luck Eddy.
Because I am your friend.
And I am here to help you.
When I was about twelve
thirteen
I was a real shit.
Fights.
Girls.
Broken windows.
One day, my Dad catches me
smoking.
Usual teenage bullshit, right?
No problem, right?
Except
he'd watched his Mum
my Grandmother
die of lung cancer.
And he'd be damned if he'd have
the same thing happen to his son.
So.
He takes the packet
and tells me to smoke the
entire thing.
I was sick as a dog, but.
I tell you.
I never smoked another
cigarette.
You think your boy over there
can tell us how much this weighs?
About an ounce.
Didn't need scales or anything.
Are you serious?
Even half that would kill him.
Every day he's killing himself.
Every day.
Here.
Please...
Anything worth doing.
Comes with a certain level of
risk, that's what my Dad taught me.
You get through this.
I guarantee you'll never touch
this shit again.
Don't listen to him Ed, he's
just trying to fuck with you.
Oh, you think they're looking
out for you like I am?
Right?
Alright, alright.
Okay, okay.
One... two... three... four.
Why don't you help him out?
All this will boil his fucking
brains, let's be honest but
a fifth of it...
You might all just get through
that.
Course, that mean going back to
square one.
All those months...
Years
of recovery, just...
Gone.
But I'm sure he's totally worth
it.
Right?
Guys?
Please don't let him kill me.
Don't let him kill me.
Please.
Twenty eight grams.
An ounce is about twenty eight
grams.
That's five point six each.
Jesus.
Had a mate do three once.
His heart was pounding like you
wouldn't believe
his temperature went through
the roof
his muscles seized up.
Didn't even yell for help.
He couldn't.
Maybe... maybe we have more of a
tolerance.
Yeah? Maybe it's cut with
baking soda or some shit..
- I don't know...
- Maybe? How can you not know what's in there?
Look, I just sell it, alright? I don't
know what it's fucking cut with.
Fantastic.
So I could end up with a nostril
full of ground glass or baking soda?
You really have no way of
knowing what's in there?
If we don't do this, we might as
well be pulling the trigger ourselves.
Okay, you go first then.
Or him, or her
I owe him shit.
You're a fucking coward Henry.
I'll do it.
We're a support group, right?
It's good.
Safe.
Carries on like this, you just
might be in luck.
So what? What? We gonna do this?
Bit more... bit more.
Fuck!
Yes, God.
This guy, this guy...
Two years.
That's what black means right?
Two years?
I doubt they've got more than
two years between them.
That's why it's so easy for them
to throw it all away. But you?
You have a future.
A son.
Don't listen to him Charley, he's
just trying to get inside your head.
You have to ask yourself.
Is he worth throwing it all
away for?
I can't.
I can't do this.
What? No.
Look, where are you going? She
doesn't mean it.
Tell him you don't mean it.
Tell him you'll do it.
I'm so sorry.
I promised my son I wouldn't
let him down. I promised.
I promised.
Well sure looks like you two
have got your work cut out.
You bastard.
I didn't do this.
Every decision, every choice - choices
he made - has brought him to this point.
No, that's not true. He's
trying to get better, he's trying.
You think he's going to have
some epiphany?
He's gonna stop?
Turn it all around?
He's not.
If he doesn't die tonight, he's
dead in six months. A year tops.
Are we gonna do this or what?
Go on then.
What are you waiting for?
We're not finished yet.
Hey!
Hey Jack, can't you see that
she's had enough?
Yeah, I can hear her fucking
heart pounding from here.
Kara
Kara, you're not gonna save
him. Not like this.
For fuck's sake, you're gonna
kill yourself!
What do I look like? Some kind
of light weight?
What is driving that engine of
yours?
Aw Jesus.
I think you've had enough for
tonight sweetheart.
No... stop. Stop.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do you think she'd be saying that if
she knew that this was all your fault?
Do you know.
I was hurting for so long
but this
this gave me freedom.
Gave me a reason to keep
breathing.
You sent me this letter.
You helped me.
All this
was you.
It can't be. It can't be.
Yes it can.
A going away present.
You earned it.
Hey, hey Jack! You ain't gotta
do this.
Yeah... I-I-I can do some more...
Okay? W-W-We can all do some
more if someone would fucking help.
I'm done man and you are too.
If you don't do this
they all die.
One by one, they all die.
Sorry, it's my fault I...
I didn't...
I'm sorry.
Sorry...
You keep saying that.
Sorry for what?
Leave her alone, she's had
enough.
No she hasn't.
You know for someone who's lost
everything
I've never known anyone cling
on as much as you.
What's your secret?
Muh-muh...
Oh it looks like we're having a
breakthrough.
Muh-muh...
Mother?
Is that what it's come to?
Murderer.
Murderer?
Why can you not appreciate what
it is I'm trying to do here?
- You killed Ellen... Dave... Eddy...
- Oh no, no, no. Don't you dare... Don't you dare!
You... you brought this on
yourselves.
These... these lives you live.
The things you do., the...
Fuck. You fucking know it.
You fucking know.
Get off me! Get off me!
What would someone have to do
to deserve this?
One. Two. Three.
I mean, they'd really have to
hate themselves for it, right?
Four. Five. Six.
So imagine you have a daughter.
A little girl.
And she meant everything to you.
No...
Imagine the people that were
supposed to help her.
As you can see we have
a new face this evening.
My name's Beck.
Hello Beck.
Take advantage of her.
Spread your toes. You
don't want to leave any marks.
Drag her down to their level.
And they leave her there to die.
- Beck? We were just there... we were just...
- Kara, Kara, look at me...
Kara look at me. Look at me
Kara.
We need to get the fuck out of
here right now, okay?
What do you think they'd
deserve?
One cut?
Three?
How much to make that right?
Oh my god...
Oh my god it's him.
What the fuck is this? What's
going on?
What did you fucking do?
Beck.
That's who we are talking about
right?
Y'know, she always said her dad
was nuts.
Oh, is that right?
She'd fallen off the program.
She needed help.
So she came to you?
Yeah, cause she was scared of
you.
Afraid of what you'd do, in case you found
out that she got kicked out the group.
Charley spoke to me, I spoke to
some people and got what she needed.
What she needed...
We were trying to help her
through withdrawal.
Couple of days, that's all it
was.
We'd take turns watching her.
She didn't want to be alone.
Spread your toes. You don't
want to leave any marks.
Kara...
Please don't go.
And I wasn't strong enough.
Beck? Beck? Hey, hey
Beck?
Kara, Kara get the fuck up.
What the fuck is going on?
Beck, look at me. Open your
eyes.
Kara? Kara, call a fucking
ambulance!
What the fuck did you do? What
the fuck did you do?
Kara call a fucking ambulance!
I didn't know she was still on
the script.
You should never use when
you're still on the script.
You left her in some fucking
shit hole!
My little girl.
It wasn't her fault.
Oh I keep hearing that.
It's not my fault... I didn't do
this... I don't deserve this.
It was my idea to dry her out.
My idea to leave her there. I...
I sold it to her.
I thought that was the person
that I wanted to be. It wasn't.
And it was a fucking shit way
to find out but...
If anyone deserves this, it's
me. No-one else.
Well, they didn't stop you,
they didn't help her.
Didn't speak up.
It wasn't like that.
If they'd of found out what
we'd done.
They would never have let me
see my son again.
I couldn't risk that happening,
I couldn't...
Yes, you could!
But you didn't.
You had a choice.
Just like him, like her...
And look how it worked out for
them.
Mate, mate this has got.
Shut up!
When I came here, I said one
thing above all things.
Prove to me you deserve to walk
out that door.
The only thing you've proven, is
that you're liars, junkies, cheats...
Monsters, one and all.
It's not true. It's not.
Give me one good reason why I
shouldn't fucking kill them now.
Seth takes his nephew out and
plays football with him every weekend.
Every weekend.
And Charley loves her son. She
loves him so much.
And Henry might be a prick but
he hasn't killed anybody.
He didn't even know she existed.
Go on. Get the fuck out of here.
He's going nowhere.
- Come on, come on. Think about your boy!
- What about Seth? What about Seth?
Seth!
You missed someone.
Or maybe you didn't.
A life for a life.
Whose fault is it?
You?
Or you?
Jack, Jack we both know it's me.
No Seth, it's not. It's my
fault.
I'm everything he says I am.
It's my fault.
Jack, it's my fault. It's me.
- No, Seth. No-one else needs to die because of me.
- Kara. Kara, it's fine really.
- No, please, please.
- Kara. Kara!
It's okay.
What do I do?
Just live.
It's not just enough to know
what you've done...
You have to do it.
Do you feel any fucking better
now?
No. No I don't.